SAFAE QARSSANE

Full Stack Developer



+212 608-956657



qarssane.safae@gmail.com



Safare Qarssane

PROFILE

I'm a full-stack developer specializing in the creation of websites using technologies such as ReactJS, Next.js, Laravel, Vue.js and React Native. My skills also extend to database management, with in-depth mastery of SQL and PostgreSQL. I'm an assertive all-rounder, and have successfully contributed to a variety of projects, both on the web and on mobile.

EDUCATION

Web and mobile development

YouCode Maroc 2020 - 2022

Youssoufia

English studies

Cadi Ayyad University 2018 - 2020

Marrakech

Baccalaureat science physique

Ijtihad High School 2017 – 2018

Youssoufia

SKILLS

Javascript

Typescript

Node.j:

Nest.js

php Laravel

MySql

MongoDB

React.js

Vue.js

React Native

Html/Css

Git/Github

Agile

Puppeteer/Playwright

COMPLETED PROJECTS

MAGRH

 Creation of a laravel web application for a company to correctly manage its HR requests.

COMPLAINTS MANAGEMENT

 Creation of a claims management web application using React.js, Node.js, Nest.js, typeORM.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full stack developer

Group Auceni - Full-time 10/2023 - Present

France - Remote

- Manage the development of complete solutions using Vue.js, Laravel, PHP and MySQL.
- Application deployment on Ionos servers.

Frontend developer

Im'enSe - Freelance 08/2023 - 10/2023

Tanger - Remote

 Managed the development of a dynamic web application using Next.js, React.js, and Node.js.

Full stack developer

ADSGLORY - Full time 07/2022 - 06/2023

Tanger - Onsite

- Design and implementation of a mobile application with React Native. And websites with React.js.
- Implementation of robust backend functionality with NestJS.

Wordpress Developer - Internship

Agence SEO Maroc 08/2021 - 09/2021

Casablanca - Remote

 Development and customization of WordPress websites with SEO to improve website visibility.

LANGUAGES

- English (vocational)
- Arabic (vocational)
- French (intermediate)